my100bank.com 2016-04-16

# FACTS

                                                                                              Rev 03/2016
                      WHAT DOES HOME BANCSHARES, INC. DO
FACTS                 WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                      Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
Why?                  consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                      we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                      understand what we do.
What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                            Social Security number and account balances
                            checking account information and payment history
                            account transactions and transaction history
                      When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this
                      notice.
How?                  All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                      business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                      customers’ personal information; the reasons Home BancShares, Inc. chooses to share; and
                      whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                            Does Home BancShares,
Reasons we can share your personal information                                              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                    Inc. share?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                        Yes                               No
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                        Yes                               No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                      Yes                               No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                         No                       We don’t share.
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                         No                       We don’t share.
information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                       No                       We don’t share.
Questions?            Call 1-888-372-9788 or go to www.my100bank.com

Page 2
Who we are
                                            Bank Holding Company
Who is providing this notice?
                                            Bank
                                            Insurance Agency
What we do
How does Home BancShares, Inc.          To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
protect my personal information?        and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                        These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                        and buildings.
How does Home BancShares, Inc.          We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?
                                            open an account or deposit money
                                            pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                            use your credit or debit card
                                        We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                        bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?          Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                            sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                             about your creditworthiness
                                            affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                            sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                        State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                        limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                              Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                        financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                            Home BancShares, Inc. does not share with our affiliates.
Nonaffiliates                           Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                        financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                             Home BancShares, Inc. does not share with nonaffiliates so they
                                             can market to you.
Joint Marketing                         A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                        together market financial products or services to you.
                                            Our joint marketing partners include investment companies and
                                             insurance companies.
List of Affiliates
     Home BancShares, Inc.
     Centennial Bank
     Centennial Insurance Agency, Inc.
     Cook Insurance Agency, Inc.
     Freedom Insurance Group, Inc
